Pavel Tarasov

Birth year: 1990 | City: Kiriat Yam, Israel | LinkedIn

Email: pavel.a.tarasov@gmail.com | Telegram: @tarasov pavel | Phone: 058-406-1464

Summary:

I have 6+ years of experience in server-side development. I have been developing DWH with ETL processes, data input forms and OLAP reports. I have been implementing business logic in PL/SQL. Now I am learning Hebrew on MASA in Kiriat Yam.

Professional skills: SQL (Oracle), PL/SQL, C#, Python

Languages: Russian: native; English: B1.

Experience:

02.2015 – 09.2019 Pro IT Resource – Oracle developer Perm, Russia

Development and support of OLAP financial data monitoring systems.

The business logic of the systems was implemented as PL/SQL packages. Main tasks which were implemented:

- Data loading from external systems in form of incremental daily updates in XML;
- Maintenance of various directories and indicators, data input according to them;
- Development of OLAP reports based on input data.

10.2018 – 05.2019	KIBERone – Tutor	Perm, Russia
07.2013 - 02.2015	ER-Telecom – Oracle developer	Perm, Russia

- Support of the Equipment Manager system (network equipment accounting system);
- Finalization of the electronic document management system in Equipment Manager: transferring documents to 1C and billing system;

12.2010 – 08.2012	JSC PROGNOZ – Junior tester	Perm, Russia
09.2008 - 08.2010	The Perm State Regional Universal Library named after A.M.Gorky – Computer lab administrator	Perm, Russia

Education:

2011 – 2017	Perm National Research Polytechnic University Electrical Engineering Faculty, speciality: automated control and information processing systems (extramural, incomplete)
2007 – 2010	Perm State National Research University Faculty of Mechanics and Mathematics, speciality: mechanics, applied mathematics (incomplete)

Hobbies and other activity: I like running, fencing and hiking. I have experience as a volunteer.